[
    {
        "question": "Are you male?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter1",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "gender"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you female?",
        "answer": "No",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter1",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "gender"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Are you non-binary?",
        "answer": "No",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter1",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "gender"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have hair?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter2",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "appearance"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Is your hair color blue?",
        "answer": "No",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter2",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "appearance"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have blue eyes?",
        "answer": "No",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter2",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "appearance"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you have a moustachio?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter2",
        "themes": [
            "people",
            "appearance"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Is your mother names kayle?",
        "answer": "No",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter3",
        "themes": [
            "relatives",
            "people"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Is your father names marc?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter3",
        "themes": [
            "relatives",
            "people"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Is your brother names maximilian?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter3",
        "themes": [
            "relatives",
            "people"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Is your dog names smooky the bandito?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "source": "BookOfLife",
        "subject": "Chapter3",
        "themes": [
            "relatives",
            "people"
        ],
        "seen": 0
    }
]